Artifacts Register, 1879-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
- Class Pin/1909, 455; 1/2" gold
  Diamond-shaped "SC" with "09" raised in center.
- Class Pin/1909, 456; 1/2" gold
  Belonged to Rachel T. Little 1909.
- Class Pin/1910, 457; 1/2" gold
  S forming oval with "C" and "10" inside.
- Class Pin/1910, 458; 1/2" gold
- Class Pin/1910, 459; 1/2" gold
- Class Pin/1914, 460; 1/2" gold
  SC forming shield shape with "14" in center.
- Class Pin/1914, 461; 0.5" gold
- Class Pin/1915, 462; 1/4" gold
  SC in pointed oval with "15" in center.
  Belonged to Louise Egbert.
  Fine
- Class Pin/1915, 463; 1/4" gold
  Belonged to Katharine S. Pearce.
- Class Pin/1916, 464; 1/2" Gold
  S and elongated "C" set at right angles; "1916" inset.
  Belonged to Elizabeth L. Clarke, rec'd 11/77.
- Class Pin/1917, 465; 1/4" Gold
  SC forming a square with "17" in center.
  Belonged to Amy Ford.
- Class Pin/1917, 466; 1/4" Gold
  Belonged to Dorothy Cole.
- Class Pin/1917, 467; 1/4" Gold
- Class Pin/1918, 468; 1/4" Gold
  S18C in a circle.
  Belonged to Clara Curtiss.
- Pin/1924, 469; 1" Metal, plastic
  Button-style; white with blue lettering. Reads "For Smith Insurance" and "1924".
  Belonged to Lois Cole Taylor 1924.
  A bit rusty
- Class Pin/1978, 470; 1 3/4" across Metal, Plastic
  Button-style; red with white lettering. Reads "1978 The First Incompetent Class."
  Rusty
- Class Pin/1978, 471; 1 3/4" across Metal, plastic
  Button-style; red with white lettering. Reads "1978 We're Number One (hundred)."
- Alpha Club Pin/ 1881, 472; 3/4" Gold
  Stylized, angular "A."
  Belonged to Marion Hobart Cunningham 1881, given by Marion Freeman 1914.
- Alpha Club Pin/ 1881, 473; 3/4" Gold
  Belonged to Harriete M. Dunton 1881.
- Alpha Club Pin/ 1882, 474; 3/4" Gold
  Belonged to Nina E. Browne 1882.
  Okay
- Alpha Club Pin/ 1899, 475; 3/4" Gold
  Belonged to Miriam Choate 1899.
- Alpha Club Pin/ 1901, 476; 3/4" Gold
  Belonged to Charlotte DeForest 1901.
- Alpha Club Pin/ 1905, 477; 3/4" Gold
  Belonged to Florence Bannard 1905.
- Alpha Club Pin/ 1912, 478; 3/4" Gold
  Belonged to Lucia Maria Houpt 1912.
- Banjo/Mandolin Club Pin/1912, 479; 3/4" Gold
  Shape of a mandolin, with "S.M.C." in white at base.
  Belonged to Katharine Martindale 1912.
  Excellent
- Banjo/Mandolin Club Pin/N.D., 480; 3/4" Gold
  Circle with banjo across center; "Smith College Banjo Club" around circle.
  Initials H.C.M.
- Banjo/Mandolin Club Pin/1917, 481; 3/4" Gold
  Shape of a mandolin, with "S.M.C." in black at base.
  Belonged to Dorothy L. Cole 1917.
- Biological Society Pin/ N.D., 482; 1/2" Gold, enamel
  Black diamond shape with linear gold pattern.
  Initials A.C.H.
- Biological Society Pin/ N.D., 483; 1/2" Gold, enamel
- Biological Society Pin/ 1900, 484; 1/2" Gold, enamel
  Belonged to Julia C. Paton 1900.
- Biological Society Pin/ 1909, 485; 1/2" Gold, enamel
- Biological Society Pin/ 1915, 486; 1/2" Gold, enamel
  Belonged to Louise Egbert 1915.
- Biological Society Pin/ 1904, 487; 1/2" Gold, enamel
  Belonged to Dr. Anna Q. Churchill 1904.
- Colloquium Pin/1895, 488; 1/8" gold
  Shape of an inkwell. Reddish gold.
  Belonged to Caroline M. Fuller 1895.
- Colloquium Pin/1917, 489; 1/8" gold
  Belonged to Amy Ford 1917.
- Colloquium Pin/1918, 490; 1/8" gold
  Belonged to Margery Alden 1918.
- Current Events Club Pin/N.D., 491; 1/4" Enamel, gold
  Bluish-black and gold, showing the western hemisphere.
  Pattern faded
- Debating Union Pin/1922, 492; 1/2" Gold
  Squat "D" on top of elongated "U."
  Belonged to Eleanor Evans 1922.
- French Club Pin/1908, 493; 1/2" Gold, enamel
  Round with black enamel circle in center; gold fleur-de-lis in circle. "La Societe Francaise" in black around edge.
  Belonged to Angela Shipman ex-1908. Given 01/59.
- French Club Pin/1905, 494; 1/2" Gold, enamel
- German Club Pin/1915, 495; 1/4" Gold, enamel
  Shape of shield: top blue, middle white, bottom red. Gold eagle in center.
- German Club Pin/N.D., 496; 1/4" Gold, enamel
- German Club Pin/1904, 497; 1/4" Gold, enamel
- Glee Club Pin/ 1918, 498; 1/4" Gold
  G-clef crossed by tuning fork.
  Belonged to Clara L. Curtiss 1918.
- Greek Club Pin/ N.D., 499; 1/2" Gold
- Greek Club Pin/ N.D., 500; 1/2" Gold
- Greek Club Pin/ 1909, 501; 1/2" Gold
- Greek Club Pin/ 1915, 502; 1/2" Gold
- Greek Club Pin/ N.D., 503; 1/2" Gold
  Given by Kara Tatro, Fin. Aid Office 04/81.
  Tarnished
- Italian Club Pin/1914, 504; 1/2" Metal
  Circle with image of Italy in center; "Il Tricolore" down center of Italy.
  Belonged to Nellie R. Elgutter 1914.
- Latin Club Pin?/1928, 505; 1/2" Gold
  Round with image of columned building. "S" and "C" on either side; "Provident" below.
  Belonged to Lucy Kendrew 1928.
- LUBA Club Pin/N.D., 506; 1/4" Gold, enamel
  Angular "SC" with banner reading "LUBA" across middle. LUBA stands for Let Us Be Acquainted.
  Given by Dorothy O'Donnell Garvey. Ack: MB 3/6/84
- Manuscript Club Pin/N.D., 507; 1/2" Gold
  Old English-style "MS."
  Given by Elizabeth L. Clarke. Rec'd 11/77.
- Mathematics Club Pin/1911, 508; 3/4" metal
  Shape of a curved triangle with an integration sign. Black with grey sign. See accompanying documentation.
  Belonged to Minerva King 1911.
- Mathematics Club Pin/1915, 509; 3/4" metal
- Mathematics Club Pin/1917, 510; 3/4" metal
- Mitten Club Pin/1904, 511; 1/8" Gold
  Shape of a tiny mitten!
  Belonged to Elizabeth W. Mason 1904.
- Olla Podrida Pin/N.D., 512; 3/4" Gold, enamel
  Elaborate, reddish-gold "O" and "P" with black enamel stew-pot at center. See accompanying documentation.
  Initials A.B.J.?
- Olla Podrida Pin/1882, 513; 3/4" Gold, enamel
  Elaborate, reddish-gold "O" and "P" with black enamel stew-pot at center.
  Belonged to Isabel D. McKee 1882.
- Oriental Club Pin/1915, 514; 0.5" gold, other metal
  Antelope (?) head with serpent tail; tail forms a circle and ends in antelope's mouth.
- Oriental Club Pin/1909, 515; 0.5" gold, other metal
- Oriental Club Pin/1917, 516; 0.5" gold, other metal
- Oriental Club Pin/N.D., 517; 0.5" gold, other metal
- Phi Beta Kappa Pin/1906, 518; 1" gold
  Belonged to Betty Amerman 1906. Sent by Mrs. Bean, her daughter, 2/76.
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1895, 519; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Three, white, inverted triangles alternated with three gold fleur-de-lis in a circle with a pearl at the center. Greek letters Phi, Kappa, Psi in gold on white triangles.
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1896, 520; 0.75" gold, enamel
  See Item #519.
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1902, 521; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Ruth French 1902.
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1910, 522; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Frederica (Buckley) Spencer 1910.
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1911, 523; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Catharine Hooper 1911.
  pearl missing
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1915, 524; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Elizabeth L. Clarke 1915. Given 11/77.
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1914, 525; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Madeleine Meyer 1914.
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1917, 526; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Margaret Alling 1917.
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1917, 527; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Virginia (Whitmore) Kelly 1917. Given by Virginia Kelly Gosnell 1944, 6/80.
  okay-dull
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1924, 528; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Elizabeth (Taylor) Butterworth 1924.
  clasp broken
- Phi Kappa Psi Pin/1907, 529; 0.75" gold, enamel
  See Item #519. See accompanying documentation.
  Belonged to ? Allison, 1907.
- Philosophical Society Pin/ N.D., 530; 0.5" gold, enamel
  Round and black with Greek inscription in gold around edge. Profile of man's head wreathed in laurel in gold in center.
  Given by Karen Tatro in Fin. Aid Office, 4/81.
- Philosophical Society Pin/ N.D., 531; 0.5" gold, enamel
- Philosophical Society Pin/ N.D., 532; 0.5" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Louise S. Fuller.
- Philosophical Society Pin/ 1904, 533; 0.5" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Anna Russ 1904
- Philosophical Society Pin/ 1909, 534; 0.5" gold, enamel
- Philosophical Society Pin/ 1915, 535; 0.5" gold, enamel
- Philosophical Society Pin/ 1915, 536; 0.5" gold, enamel
- Philosophical Society Pin/ 1920, 537; 0.5" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Allace Miriam Cowen 1920.
- Physics Club Pin/1917, 538; 1/8" gold
  Shape of a transistor?
  Belonged to Anita (Girdwood) Yearance 1917.
- Press Board Pin/1915, 539; 0.25" gold, enamel
  Black, buoy-shaped with "SC" and "PB" in gold.
  Belonged to Elizabeth L. Clarke 1915, 11/77.
- Press Board Pin/N.D., 540; 0.25" gold, enamel
- Press Board Pin/N.D., 541; 0.25" gold, enamel
- S Pin/1928, 542; 0.5" gold
  Belonged to Margaret Ogden.
  clasp will not open
- Social Science Club Pin/1922, 543; 0.25" gold
  Torch with "SSC" down the front.
- Telescopium Society Pin/ N.D., 544; 0.5" metal
  Round and convex with image of the sun in the center and the astrological signs around the edge. See accompanying documentation.
- Telescopium Society Pin/ N.D., 545; 0.5" gold
  Round and flat with image of the sun in the center and the astrological signs around the edge.
- Telescopium Society Pin/ 1912, 546; 0.5" metal
  Round and convex with image of the sun in the center and the astrological signs around the edge.
- Telescopium Society Pin/ 1917, 547; 0.5" metal
  Belonged to Dprothy L. Cole 1917.
- Telescopium Society Pin/ 1928, 548; 0.5" metal
  Belonged to Lucy E. Kendrew 1928.
- Stamp Block/N.D., 549; 7.5" x 4.25" x 1" wood, metal
  Sports Guide at Twelve Colleges for Women. Depicts women engaged in sporting events and features the names of twelve women's colleges.
- Cigarette Case/N.D., 550; 5.25" x 3" x 3/8" brass
  Angular "SC" on top, press-button clasp. Inside brushed in decorative pattern.
- Plaque and Nameplate/ 1935, 551; 7" across x .5" thick; nmplt 4.5" long pewter?
  Round plaque with bas-relief of Rebecca Wilder Holmes, Professor of Music 1903-1936. Nameplate bears her name and "1935."
  Arrived with Music Department records.
  01A-106
  scratched
- Pin Pillow/1907, 552; 4" x 4" cloth, lace, metal
  Pink satin pillow in white-and-sage decorative display pillowcase. Bordered in lace. Five pins attached: Mandolin Club, French Club, Class of 1907, Phi Kappa Psi, Alpha Society, white "SC" pin.
  Belonged to Anna (Reynolds) Morse 1907.
- Smith College Handkerchief/ c. 1955, 553; 12" x 12" cloth
  White handkerchief with green images depicting scenes of Smith College.
  belonged to and donated by Mary Chrisman Anderson '59 while she was in school
  02A-45
- Westchester Smith Club 50th Anniversary Scarf/N.D., 554; 13" x 51" polyester or nylon
  White scarf with gold diamonds with the initials "SC" inside each diamond shape One corner contains words "Westchester Smith Club 50th Anniversary"
  donated by Mary Chrisman Anderson '59
- Dissecting Tools/1959, 555; 3" x 7" plastic, metal, wood
  Blue plastic case that snaps shut with 2 scalpels, 2 tweezers, 2 pairs of scissors, 2 pokers
  belonged to and donated by Mary Chrisman Anderson '59 used for Zoology 11 and Zoology 22.
- Class Pin/1905, 556; 1/2" Metal
  Entwined square "SC"; "1905" in center. See accompanying documentation.
  Given by Patricia Hampoon Wheeler 1941, via Emily Jerome at the Alumnae Fund. 9 or 10/2001. Original owner was a relative of a friend of Ms. W's.
- 50th Anniversary Pin/1925, 557; 2" x 1" Metal
  Button-style, oval-shaped, bronze-colored. Reads "Smith College '11 1875 1925" in black.
  Belonged to Althea Marks 1911. Rec'd at Reunion May 1976.
- 50th Anniversary Pin/1925, 558; 2" x 1" Metal
  Button-style, oval-shaped, bronze-colored. Reads "Smith College '16 1875 1925" in black.
  Belonged to Lucile Driscoll 1916.
- 1906 Reunion Pin/1936, 559 a-b; 2" x 1 1/2" Metal
  Button-style, oval-shaped; white with red lettering. Reads "Smith College '06 1906-1936." Two pins.
- Political Button/1984, 560; 2" across metal, plastic
  Round white button with black lettering: "Smith for Mondale, Ferraro."
  Given by Maurice Isserman, Prof. of History at Hamilton College, Clinton, NY 13323
- Rally Day Button/2001, 561 a-b; 2" across metal, plastic
  Round, yellow button with "Smith College 2001" in red and "Rally Day" in blue. Two pins.
- Otelia Cromwell Day Button/2001-02, 562; 1 0.75" across metal, plastic
  Yellow, green, and blue background with black lettering. Reads "I speak to challenge you. You challenge me by speaking."
- SC Pin/1922, 563; pin 0.75" box 1.5" x 1" gold, paper, satin
  Gold diamond-shaped pin with "SC" in white enamel. See Item #411 for more information. In original Tiffany box.
  Belonged to Katharine M. Miller 1922.
- Seal Pin/1902, 564; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Seal in gold surrounded by white enamel with "Smith College 1871" and the college motto in Greek around the edge in gold. See accompanying documentation.
  Belonged to Clara Curtiss 1918. See accompanying doc. for other owners.
- Seal Pin/1904, 565; 1" gold, enamel
  See Item #564.
- Seal Pin/1904, 566; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Elizabeth Mason 1904
- Seal Pin/1906, 567; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Susan Tanner Larkin 1906. Given by daughter, E. L. Beardsley, 5/79.
- Seal Pin/1915, 568; 0.75" gold, enamel
- Pin/1903, 569; 0.75" gold
  Appears to be in the form of a Spanish centime. Significance unknown.
- Alpha Society Stick Pin/1881, 570; 2" long gold, metal
  Alpha pin on stick.
  Belonged to Eliza P. Huntington 1881.
- Alpha Society Stick Pin/N.D., 571; 2" long gold, metal
- Alpha Society Stick Pin/N.D., 572; 2" long gold, metal
  Alpha pin on stick. See accompanying documentation.
- Colloquium Society Stick Pin/N.D., 573; 2" long gold
  Colloquium pin on stick.
- Colloquium Society Stick Pin/N.D., 574; 2" long gold
- Colloquium Society Stick Pin/1896, 575; 2" long gold
- Greek Club Stick Pin/N.D., 576; 2.25" long metal
  Owl with outstretched wings on stick. "Greek Club" on banner across owl.
- AOH Stick Pin/N.D., 577; 1 0.75" long metal, enamel
  Three-leaved green enamel shamrock on stick. From Ancient Order of Hibernians.
- SC Stick Pin/1912, 578; 1 0.75" long metal
  Diamond-shaped "SC" on stick.
  From estate of Mary E. Storer 1912. Given by Mrs. Joel Care Elty, 9/81.
- Wishbone Stick Pin/1906, 579; 1.5" long metal
  Wishbone on stick. Worn on Commencement dress of M. Gail Tritch 1906. Other significance unknown.
  Belonged to M. Gail Tritch 1906.
- SC Pin/1916, 580; 0.75" gold, enamel
  Belonged to Marjorie B. Smith 1916.
- Seal Pin/1916, 581; 0.5" gold, enamel
  Seal in gold surrounded by white enamel with "Smith College 1871" and the college motto in Greek around the edge in gold.
- Seal Pin/1916, 582; 1/8" gold
  Seal in gold with "Smith College 1871" and the college motto in Greek around the edge.
- Smith Pin/1916, 583; 1/8" gold, enamel, pearl
  Black enamel triangle in gold setting with gold "S" in center. Two tiny pearls set on each side of triangle.
- First Senior Pin/N.D., 584; 1" across gold, stones
  Owl with outstretched wings and gemstone eyes encircled by snakes, also with gemstone eyes. See accompanying documentation.
- Unicorn Pin/1974, 585; 1" across gold
  Head of unicorn. Given (by whom?) to members of Class of 1924 at 50th Reunion dinner.
  Belonged to Priscilla Rogers Hall 1924.
- Pin/1914, 586; 0.75" across metal
  Complex, four-sided design with circle in center. "SC" in center encircled by inscription "Prodesse quam conspici" with letters "CLIO" on four sides. Perhaps a history club? Significance unknown.
- Kappa Delta Pin/1907, 587; 0.5" gold, enamel
  Black shield with seven stars and Greek letters Kappa Delta in gold.
  Belonged to Clara (Senior) Iglauer 1907. Sent by dau. Laura I. Young, 6/23/80.
- Smith Pin/1907, 588; 0.75" metal, enamel
  Shape of a pennant on a pole; white with "Smith" in black.
- PC Pin/c. 1905, 589; 0.25" gold
  "P" overtop "C". Significance unknown.
  clasp does not open
- SC Hat Pin/N.D., 590; 1 0.75" wide 6" long metal
  Diamond-shaped "SC" on hat pin.
- Class Hat Pin/1915, 591; 1.5" wide 5" long metal
  Class of 1915 pin-shape on hat pin.
- Hat Pin/N.D., 592; 0.75" wide 5" long metal, stone
  Hat pin with sphere on top; studded with purple stones. Significance unknown.
- Seal Pin/N.D., 593; 0.25" gold, enamel
  Given at Reunion by Marion Preston 1942, 5/24/02.
  02A-64
- Nameplate Pin/N.D., 594; 1 0.75" x 0.75" metal, paper
  Gold-painted frame with paper inside. "Gertrude Tubby '02" on paper.
  Removed from 22. Buildings, Tenney House Round Robin
- "Save Alumnae Gym" Button/ 1976, 595; 1.5" across metal
- SC Ring/N.D., 596; 1" silver
  Silver ring with onyx/black enamel setting. Seal set into onyx.
- SC Charm/1887, 597; 1.5" long x 0.75" wide gold, enamel
  Modelled after the Phi Beta Kappa Key, with black enamel face and SC seal set in gold in center. "Smith College AD 1871" and Greek motto around seal.
  Belonged to Mary Alice Walton 1887.
- Sigma Charm?/ 1914, 598; 1.25" long x 0.75" wide gold
  Modelled after the Phi Beta Kappa Key with large Greek Sigma on face. Given to Mary Louise Foster 1891 by U. of Chicago? in 1914. Significance unknown.
  Belonged to Mary Louise Foster 1891. Sent by Mary Foster Kingimill 4/1/77.
- Smith College Monthly Pin/1879, 599; 2" long gold
  Shape of a feather/quill. See accompanying documentation under #417.
  Belonged to Kate Morris Cone 1879.
  clasp missing
- Phi Beta Kappa Charm/1879, 600; 1.25" long gold
  Standard Phi Beta Kappa Key. See accompanying documentation under #417.
- AASC Charm/N.D., 601; 1.25" long metal
  Silver-plated oval charm with Alumnae Association logo and "Alumnae Association of Smith College 1881."
  very worn
- Seal Charm/N.D., 602; 0.5" across silver
  Silver seal encircled by black enamel inscribed with "Smith College AD 1871" and Greek motto in silver.
- Class Ring/N.D., 603; 0.75" gold
  Diamond-shaped flat surface with "SC" and either "02" or "20".
  Envelope in which ring was found reads "Hannah Scharps 1906" but ring appears to be from either 1902 or 1920 and has the initials K.A. inscribed.
- Seal Charm/1899, 604; 0.75" silver
  Seal in silver with while enamel around edge. "Smith College AD 1871" and Greek motto in gold.
- Handbag/N.D., 605; 11" x 9" cloth
  Beige handbag with cream satin lining. Red felt circle on front with "94" in white. Used at an 1894 Class Reunion.
  Pulled from 80. Class of 1894 records.
  has burlap smell
- Theatre Department T-shirt/N.D., 606; size S cotton
  White cotton t-shirt with "Theatre 14," "Smith College Theatre Department," and names and dates of plays in yellow and black.
  Pulled from 52. Theatre Department records.
- Theatre Department Tote Bag/1985, 607; 13" x 13" canvas
  Cream canvas with red handles. Flower design and Theatre Dept. 1984-85 season play titles printed in purple.
- Theatre Department Tote Bag/1984, 608; 12" x 14" canvas
  Cream canvas with navy blue trim, handles, and print, featuring 1983-84 season play titles. Extra-long handles.
- Reunion Costume/1967, 609; 22" skirt 8" x 5" bag 2" wide h'nd cloth
  Class of 1937 30th Reunion costume: yellow skirt, handbag, and headband with ruler pattern on all pieces.
  Pulled from 80. Class of 1937 records.
- T-shirt/1984, 610; size M cotton/ poly
  Blue t-shirt with white lettering. Reads "We're Moving 84ward. Smith College." White banner found with t-shirt has identical lettering without "Smith College," and has been discarded.
  Pulled from 80. Class of 1984 records
- Reunion Costume/1934, 611; 14" hood 12" hbg plastic
  Class of 1933 first reunion costume plastic yellow hood and handbag. Nametags in shape of umbrellas. See accompanying documentation.
  Pulled from 80. Class of 1933 records. Nametags are for H. Hansen and E. Sturgis.
  soiled and strong plastic smell
- Reunion Costume/1963, 612; 15" x 8 1/2" canvas
  Class of 1943 20th Reunion costume: green canvas "tool belt" with toold printed in white in pockets. "43" in center.
  Pulled from 80. Class of 1943 records.
- Reunion Costume/1953, 613; 14" x 8" canvas
  Class of 1943 10th Reunion costume: large four-fingered green mitt.
- Reunion Costume/1973, 614; 14" strand wood
  Class of 1943 30th Reunion costume (part): green beads on green cord.
- Reunion Costume/1968, 615; 10" long ribbon, paper
  Class of 1943 25th Reunion costume (part): green prize ribbon with white paper center. Blank.
- Reunion Costume/N.D., 616; 5 1/2" long plastic
  Class of 1943 Reunion prop: green bubble pipe with white stem.
  gob of lip- stick on end
- Reunion Costume/N.D., 617; 3 1/2" across plastic
  Class of 1943 Reunion prop: green and white button reading "I like 43".
- Reunion Costume/1974, 618; 10" across plastic
  Class of 1944 30th Reunion hat: blue 45 with attachments to tie to head.
  Pulled from 80. Class of 1944 records.
  slightly cracked
- Reunion Costume/1954, 619; 10" x 10" paper, cloth
  Class of 1944 10th Reunion hat: purple mortarboard with white tassle. "44" on front in white.
  discolored
- Reunion Costume/N.D., 620; 12" across cloth
  Class of 1944 Reunion bag: navy blue with white trim. Round, like bowling bag.
- Reunion Costume/1991, 621; 14" x 9" canvas
  Class of 1946 45th Reunion bag: red canvas with white image of Dewey and "1946 This, The House We Live In" in white.
  Pulled from 80. Class of 1946 records.
- Reunion Costume/1991, 622; 8 1/2" long metal, plastic, etc.
  Class of 1946 Reuniun favor: watch with black band, white face, image of Dewey and "1946" in red. In black case.
- Gym Uniform and Bathing Suit/1942, 623; various sizes cloth
  Two-piece red gym suit (heavy jumpsuit, v-neck sweater) and tennis-dress-style bathing suit.
  Belonged to Dorothy M. Watson 1942. Rec'd 5/23/97.
  97A- 83
- Fan/N.D., 624; 10" x 8" straw, ribbon
  Oval-shaped purple straw fan decorated with flowers and ribbon. Significance unknown.
- Button/N.D., 625; 3 1/4" across plastic, metal
  Green button with "Smith 1931" in black and strip of silver reflective tape in center. Reunion prop?
- Wood Block/1948-49, 626; 5 1/2" x 5 1/2" wood
  Block of carved wood commemorating Pompeiana exhibit, SCMA, 1948-49.
  Pulled from 22. Buildings, Museum.
  faded
- Dumbbells/ 1881, 627; 9" each wood
  Two wooden hand-dumbbells. See accompanying documentation.
  Belonged to Anna M. Hoyt 1881.
- Stamp Block/N.D., 628; 3" x 2" copper
  Copper stamp block with "The Washburn House" in reverse type.
- Plate from Portrait/N.D., 629; 3" metal
  Nameplate from portrait of Ellen Emerson Davenport 1901.
- Smith Banner/ N.D., 630; felt
  Brick-red felt with "Smith" in white.
  Belonged to Margaret Enella Beckley 1914.
  has some holes
- Wedgwood PlatesN.D., 631; 10.5" acr. china
  Depicting Wilson House and Neilson Library (two plates) in rose in center of plate; cream border with raised pattern.
  Belonged to Lois Hall 1930. Given by Faith Barrington 6/2001.
- Wedgwood Plate/N.D., 632; 10.5" acr. china
  Depicting College Hall in blue in center of plate; cream border with raised pattern.
  From New England Province Archives, Hadi Marshall.
  01A- 119
- Wedgwood Plate Set/1932, 633; 10.5" acr. china
  Entire set of dinner plates in rose. Depicting College Hall, Grecourt Gates, Sage Hall, Paradise Pond, John M. Greene Hall, Lanning Fountain, Sophia Smith Homestead, Dewey House, Seelye Hall, the Observatory, Wilson House, Neilson Library. Featuring Neilson's signature.
- SC Seal Charm/1904, 634; 1" across metal
  Seal surrounded by white, etc.
- Reunion Costume/N.D., 635; 22" wide 30" long cotton
  white asian style robe with short sleeves and yellow trim on sleeve cuffs and along front opening. Has black print on back of a circle with the letters SC in the middle and 1905.
  belonged to H. Louisa Billings, 1905
  02A-93
- Reunion Costume/N.D., 636; purse 7.5" x 6.5" mittens 7.5" x 5.5" flower? bulb 8" x 12" stem 4.5 ft. cotton
  Class of 1953 reunion costume -flat yellow purse with black bee on front flap with numerals 53 in its wings - 2 yellow cloth mittens with "53" in black on each -yellow cloth item which most closely resembles a flower with a long cloth stuffed stem
  Belonged to Betsy Jones Hayes '53
  02A-52